A dream called freedom. A nightmare called Nicaragua.
Carla's Song is a war, drama, romance film directed by Ken Loach.
A Glasgow man visits war-torn Nicaragua with a
refugee tormented by her memories.
George Lennox, played by Robert Carlyle.
Carla, played by Oyanka Cabezas.
Bradley, played by Scott Glenn.
Maureen, played by Louise Goodall.
Rafael, played by Salvador Espinoza.
George's Mother, played by Margaret McAdam.
Carla's Song is a 1996 film directed by Ken Loach and written by Paul
Laverty, that deals with the impact of the Contra War in Nicaragua.
It is a United Kingdom–Spain–Germany co-production.
The film explores themes of civil war, glasgow, scotland,
socially deprived family, bus ride, bus driver.
The tone is emotional.